First ever animated movie created for 3D
Fly Me to the Moon is a adventure, animation,
family film directed by Ben Stassen.
Three young houseflies stow away aboard the Apollo 11 flight to the moon.
Yegor (voice), played by Tim Curry.
Louie (voice), played by Robert Patrick.
Nat's Mom (voice), played by Kelly Ripa.
Nat (voice), played by Trevor Gagnon.
I.Q. (voice), played by Philip Bolden.
Nadia (voice), played by Nicollette Sheridan.
Fly Me to the Moon is a 2008 animated science fiction comedy film about three
flies who stowaway aboard Apollo 11 and travel to the Moon.
It was directed by Ben Stassen and written by Domonic Paris.
The film was released in digital 3-D in Belgium on 30 January
2008, and in the US and Canada on 15 August.
The film was also released in IMAX 3-D in the US and Canada on 8 August.
The film serves as a fictionalized retelling of the 1969 Apollo 11 mission by incorporating a story of three young flies that stow away on the rocket
to fulfill their dream of going up to the moon, while their families take on a group of Soviet flies who try to sabotage the mission.
Fly Me to the Moon was produced by nWave Pictures in association with Illuminata
Pictures, and distributed by Summit Entertainment in the United States.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics and was a box office
disappointment, only grossing $41.7 million against a $25 million budget.